Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Chemistry, Waymouth Group, Records SC1263
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Waymouth Lab Notebooks, Series 2
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 11, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 12, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 13, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 14, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 15, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 16, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - 17, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Agoston, Tony - 1, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Edwards, David - 1, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Edwards, David - EDC 4, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Hu, Yirong - 1, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Hu, Yirong - 2, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Hu, Yirong - 3 (Box 5)
  - Hu, Yirong - 4, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Hu, Yirong - 5, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Hu, Yirong - 6, 1997 (Box 5)
  - Hu, Yirong - 7, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Kamigaito, Masami - 1, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Kamigaito, Masami - 2, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Leclerc, Margaret - 1, 1996 (Box 6)
  - Leclerc, Margaret - 1, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Doshi, Rajiv - 1, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Nowick, Dave - 1, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Wischmeyer, Ulrike - 1, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Brown, David - 1, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Koh, Michelle - 1, 1994 (Box 6)
  - McMasters, Daniel R. - 1, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Sernetz, Fritz - 1, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Sernetz, Fritz - 2, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Sernetz, Fritz - 3, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Cohen, Seth M. - 1, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Cohen, Seth M. - 2, 1993 (Box 6)
  - LaPointe, Anne M. - 2, 1990 (Box 6)
  - LaPointe, Anne M. - 3, 1990 (Box 6)
  - LaPointe, Anne M. - 7, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Joseweit, Franke - 2, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Shaughnessy, Kevin - Seminar Notes, 1997 (Box 6)
  - McKnight, Andrew - Personal Notes, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Chew, Clifford - 1, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Ren, Zhong - Seminar Notes, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Polse, Jennifer - 1, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Polse, Jennifer - 2, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Sammis, Glenn - 2, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Sammis, Glenn - 3, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Aenajjar, Ihrahim - 1, 1999 (Box 8)
  - Aenajjar, Ihrahim - 2, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Maciejewski, Jennifer - 1, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Maciejewski, Jennifer - 2, 1996 (Box 8)
  - Maciejewski, Jennifer - 3, 1996 (Box 8)
  - Maciejewski, Jennifer - 4, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Maciejewski, Jennifer - 5, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Maciejewski, Jennifer - 6, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Maciejewski, Jennifer - 7, 1998 (Box 8)
  - Maciejewski, Jennifer - 8, 1999 (Box 8)
  - Maciejewski, Jennifer - 9, 1999 (Box 8)
  - Diehl, Stephen - 1, 1998 (Box 8)
  - Diehl, Stephen - 2, 1998 (Box 8)
  - Diehl, Stephen - 3, 1999 (Box 8)
  - Diehl, Stephen - 4, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Curnow, Owen - 1, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Chen, Zhongren - 1, 1998 (Box 8)
  - Chen, Zhongren - 2, 1998 (Box 8)
  - Chen, Zhongren - 3, 1999 (Box 8)
  - Brown, Geoff - 1, 1995 (Box 8)
  - Brown, Geoff - 2, 1996 (Box 8)
  - Brown, Geoff - 3, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Brown, Geoff - 4, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Eleftheriou, Antigoni - 1, 1998 (Box 8)
  - Beltran, Jesus - 1, 1997 (Box 8)
  - McQueen, S. - 1, 1997 (Box 8)
  - Finze, Maik - 1, 1999 (Box 8)
  - Finze, Maik - 2, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Finze, Maik - 3, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Lin, Shirley - 1, 1999 (Box 8)
  - Lin, Shirley - 2, 1999 (Box 8)
  - Lin, Shirley - 3, 1999 (Box 8)
  - Lin, Shirley - 4, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Lin, Shirley - 5, 1996 (Box 9)
  - Lin, Shirley - 6, 1996 (Box 9)
  - Lin, Shirley - 7, 1997 (Box 9)
  - Lin, Shirley - 8, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Lin, Shirley - 9, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Lin, Shirley - 10, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Kwan, Brian - 1, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Nakamura, Hiroshi - 1, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Nakamura, Hiroshi - 2, 1999 (Box 9)
  - Reybuck, S. E., 1999 (Box 9)
  - Straus, Daniel - 1, 1995 (Box 9)
  - Straus, Daniel - 2, 1995 (Box 9)
  - Straus, Daniel - 3, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Straus, Daniel - 4, 1997 (Box 9)
  - Straus, Daniel - 5, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Straus, Daniel - Summer, 1990 (Box 9)
  - Bowden, Ned - 1, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Bowden, Ned - 2, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Bowden, Ned - 3, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Bowden, Ned - 4, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Bowden, Ned - 5, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Bowden, Ned - 6, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Bowden, Ned - 7, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Nakamura, Hiroshi - 1, 1999 (Box 9)
  - Nakamura, Hiroshi - 2, 1999 (Box 9)
  - Nakamura, Hiroshi - 3, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Shiseoka, Neil - 1, 1999 (Box 9)
  - Fan, Wendy - 1, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Fan, Wendy - 2, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Fan, Wendy - 3, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Fan, Wendy - 4, 1999 (Box 9)
  - Fan, Wendy - 5, 1999 (Box 9)
  - Fan, Wendy - 6, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Fan, Wendy - 7, 2000 (Box 9)
  - Lin, Yuxiang - 1, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Gomez, Fernando - 1, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Gomez, Fernando - 2, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Gomez, Fernando - 3, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Gomez, Fernando - 4, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Gomez, Fernando - 5, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Reybuck, Sarah - 1, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Reybuck, Sarah - 2, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Reybuck, Sarah - 3, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Schutz, Jan - 1, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Schutz, Jan - 2, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Schutz, Jan - 3, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Chen, Wei-wei - 1, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Chen, Wei-wei - 2, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Ahn, Christina - 1, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Lavoie, Adrien - 1, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Lavoie, Adrien - 2, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Lavoie, Adrien - 3, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Lavoie, Adrien - 4, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Ma, Sandy - 1, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Ma, Sandy - 2, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Horner, Emily - 1, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Mahanthappa, Mahesh - 1, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Mahanthappa, Mahesh - 2, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Mahanthappa, Mahesh - 3, 1999 (Box 10)
  - Mahanthappa, Mahesh - 4, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Mahanthappa, Mahesh - 5, 2000 (Box 10)
  - Mahanthappa, Mahesh - 6, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Mahanthappa, Mahesh - 7, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Mahanthappa, Mahesh - 8, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Mahanthappa, Mahesh - 9, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Lau, JK - 1, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Lau, JK - 2, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Dankova, Michaela - 1, 1998 (Box 11)
  - Dankova, Michaela - 2, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Dankova, Michaela - 3, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Dankova, Michaela - 4, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Dankova, Michaela - 5, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Dankova, Michaela - 6, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Ho, Michael - 1, 1998 (Box 11)
  - Ho, Michael - 2, 1998 (Box 11)
  - Ho, Michael - 3, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Ho, Michael - 4, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Hung, Joyce - 1, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Hung, Joyce - 2, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Hung, Joyce - 3, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Hung, Joyce - 4, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Hung, Joyce - 5, 2002 (Box 11)
  - Hung, Joyce - 6, 2002 (Box 11)
  - Hung, Joyce - 7, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Fukumoto, Yoshiyu - 1, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Fukumoto, Yoshiyu - 2, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Tagge, Christopher, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Wilmes, Gregg - 1, 1998 (Box 11)
  - Wilmes, Gregg - 2, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Wilmes, Gregg - 3, 1999 (Box 11)
  - Wilmes, Gregg - 4, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Wilmes, Gregg - 5, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Wilmes, Gregg - 6, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Wilmes, Gregg - 7, 2002 (Box 11)
  - Wilmes, Gregg - 8, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Wilmes, Gregg - 9, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Kraft, Brad - 1, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Kraft, Brad - 2, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Kraft, Brad - 3, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Huang, Kuo-Wei - 1, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Huang, Kuo-Wei - 2, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Huang, Kuo-Wei - 3, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Huang, Kuo-Wei - 4, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Huang, Kuo-Wei - 5, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Huang, Kuo-Wei - 6, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Huang, Kuo-Wei - 7, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Alistar, Sabina - 1, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Lincoln, Alice - 2, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Csihony, Szilard - 1, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Csihony, Szilard - 2, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Csihony, Szilard - 3, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Csihony, Szilard - 4, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Stehling, Udo - 1, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Stehling, Udo - 2, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Kilickiran, Pinar - 1, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Kilickiran, Pinar - 2, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Zimmerman, Melanie - 1, 2005 (Box 12)
  - Benight, Stephanie - 1, 2005 (Box 12)
  - Benson, Stefan - 1, 2005 (Box 12)
  - Benson, Stefan - 2, 2006 (Box 12)
  - Dove, Andrew - 1, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Dove, Andrew - 2, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Dove, Andrew - 3, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Dove, Andrew - 4, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Dove, Andrew - 5, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Dove, Andrew - 6, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Culkin, Darcy - 1, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Scholten, Marc - 1, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Scholten, Marc - 2, 2005 (Box 13)
  - Scholten, Marc - 3, 2006 (Box 13)
  - Scholten, Marc - 4, 2008 (Box 13)
  - Payne, Bridgett - 1, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Payne, Bridgett - 1, 2005 (Box 13)
  - Kamber, Nahrain - 1, 2002 (Box 13)
  - Kamber, Nahrain - 2, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Kamber, Nahrain - 3, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Kamber, Nahrain - 4, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Kamber, Nahrain - 5, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Kamber, Nahrain - 6, 2005 (Box 13)
  - Kamber, Nahrain - 7, 2006 (Box 13)
  - Kamber, Nahrain - 8, 2007 (Box 13)
  - Ketz, Ben - 1, 2002 (Box 13)
  - Ketz, Ben - 2, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Ketz, Ben - 3, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Gonzalez, S. - 1, 2006 (Box 13)
  - Tsujii, Yasuhito - 1, 2005 (Box 13)
  - Tsujii, Yasuhito - Tsujii Jeong - 1, 2006 (Box 13)
  - Tsujii, Yasuhito - 2, 2006 (Box 13)
  - SHS - 1, 2005 (Box 13)
  - Keets, Kate - 1, 2005 (Box 13)
  - Kirn, Nicole - 1, 2007 (Box 13)
  - Coulembier, Olivier - 1, 2006 (Box 13)
  - Coulembier, Olivier - 1 (Sheet Copy), 2006 (Box 13)
  - FJ (initials) - TOEGE, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Gibson, Raymond - 1, 2008 (Box 13)
  - Jones, Alexandra - 1, 2007 (Box 13)
  - McKenzie, M. - 1, 2009 (Box 13)
  - WLN - 1, 2008 (Box 13)
  - Conley, Nick - 1, 2005 (Box 13)
  - Conley, Nick - 2, 2006 (Box 13)
  - Conley, Nick - 3, 2006 (Box 13)
  - Hedrick, P, 2010 (Box 14)
  - Allen, Ranulfo, 2009 (Box 14)
  - Jeon, SangJin - 1, 2006 (Box 14)
  - Jeon, SangJin - 2, 2006 (Box 14)
  - Jeon, SangJin - 3, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Kiesewetter, Elizabeth - 1, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Kiesewetter, Elizabeth - 2, 2006 (Box 14)
  - Kiesewetter, Elizabeth - 3, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Kiesewetter, Elizabeth - 4, 2009 (Box 14)
  - Kiesewetter, Elizabeth - 5, 2009 (Box 14)
  - Kiesewetter, Elizabeth - 6, 2010 (Box 14)
  - Jeong, Won Hee - 1, 2003 (Box 14)
  - Jeong, Won Hee - 2, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Jeong, Won Hee - 3, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Jeong, Won Hee - 4, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Jeong, Won Hee - 5, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Jeong, Won Hee - 6, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Jeong, Won Hee - 7, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Jeong, Won Hee - 8, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Jeong, Won Hee - 9, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Jeong, Won Hee - 10, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Thomaszewski, B., 2007 (Box 14)
  - Painter, Ron - 5 (Box 14)
  - Pearson, David - 1, 2006 (Box 14)
  - Pearson, David - 2, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Pearson, David - 3, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Pearson, David - 4, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Pearson, David - 5, 2009 (Box 14)
  - Pearson, David - 6, 2009 (Box 14)
  - Pearson, David - 7, 2010 (Box 14)
  - Pearson, David - 8, 2010 (Box 14)
  - Weber, Ryan - 1, 2006 (Box 14)